Hi all! After a long time I started recording
大家好！过了好久我才开始录音
not only short videos on hypnosis, brew some crumbs
不只是催眠短视频，酿造一些面包屑
tea and let's go.
喝茶，我们走吧。
On the eve of the New Year, and in this video I want to discuss how
在除夕夜，在这个视频中我想讨论如何
the two thousandth magic to come, what is left of the franchise
即将到来的第二千个魔法，特许经营权还剩下什么
alone at home, and what is known about the fate of the trolls Kuzi.
独自在家，巨魔库兹的命运又如何。
Let's start in order.
让我们按顺序开始吧。
Imagine, it's 1,999 now, they say on TV that
想象一下，现在是 1,999，他们在电视上说
This year would be difficult.
今年会很困难。
The chimes go off and the year 1,999 comes.
钟声响起，1999 年到来了。
Wait, what?
等等，什么？
Everything is quite simple.
一切都很简单。
At first there were a lot of old computers.
起初有很多旧电脑。
Which adapters with button technology could not, due to
哪些具有按钮技术的适配器不能，因为
outdated, so they could have come, either
已经过时了，所以他们也可以来
for 1.9 years, or zero year.
1.9 年，或零年。
Because of this error, I will experience
由于这个错误，我将经历
incident that led to the illusion of work, network
导致工作、网络错觉的事件
narrations.
叙述。
However, thanks to the noise raised by various
然而，由于各种噪音的影响
and with Dainias, back in 1,040-1,3 years, in 16 computers, state
和戴尼亚斯一起，早在 1,040-1.3 年前，在 16 台计算机中，状态
structures, in Bartsami now, in these initiation services
结构，现在在巴特萨米，在这些启动服务中
afterbirth
胞衣
If you ask me what movie he is socializing with
如果你问我他在跟什么电影交往
Happy New Year, then most likely he will answer 1.1.
新年快乐，那么他很可能会回答1.1。
However, why doesn’t a new one appear after 3 years?
然而，为什么3年后还没有新的出现呢？
parts?
部分？
And why is 1.4 the worst?
为什么 1.4 是最差的？
Let's start from the beginning.
让我们从头开始吧。
When this film project was launched, no one was involved in it
当这个电影项目启动时，没有人参与其中
I didn't believe it.
我不相信。
The budget was small.
预算很小。
Almost all scenes were filmed in one location.
几乎所有场景都是在一个地点拍摄的。
There were many problems during filming.
拍摄过程中出现了很多问题。
But despite this, the film about the little ass remains
但尽管如此，关于小屁股的电影仍然存在
alone at home, became successful.
独自一人在家，取得了成功。
With a budget of 15-17 million dollars, the film grossed
该片预算为 15-1700 万美元，票房收入
$4.76 million.
476万美元。
But how?
但如何呢？
It is precisely because the cinema of the pictures is different from others,
正是因为画面的影院感与其他不同，
she has become so special.
她变得如此特别。
New idea, brilliant players, and imitated
新理念、优秀选手、被模仿
caterers Maclay Culkin.
餐饮承办商麦克莱·卡尔金 (Maclay Culkin)。
Interesting fact, the scene where Maclay Culkin publishes
有趣的是，Maclay Culkin 发表的场景
cripples from Vasyon, there was complete improvisation, where I
来自 Vasyon 的残废者，完全是即兴创作，我在那里
the director liked it so much that they decided to make
导演非常喜欢它，所以他们决定制作
a reference to the film Scream in Ofishek cinema.
参考奥菲舍克电影院的电影《惊声尖叫》。
Also, the movie is an angel with a dirty face who
另外，这部电影是一个长着脏脸的天使，
Cavin looks in the film, does not exist in reality.
卡文在电影中看起来，在现实中并不存在。
This once again proves that the film was worked on
这再次证明了这部电影是经过精心制作的
great job.
干得好。
There are, of course, franchises waiting for sequels.
当然，还有一些特许经营权正在等待续集。
The film 1-dom-2 does not introduce anything new, since
电影 1-dom-2 没有引入任何新内容，因为
its concept remains the same.
它的概念保持不变。
So, Kevin now has space in a two-story house
所以，凯文现在有一栋两层楼的房子
New York scene.
纽约场景。
Take these 20 million dollars, the film collected
拿这2000万块钱，电影收了
about 359 million dollars.
约3.59亿美元。
Due to interests, we can say that the first part
由于兴趣，我们可以说第一部分
became so popular that when they filmed the second one,
变得如此受欢迎，以至于当他们拍摄第二部时，
people knew the actors and interfered with the filming.
人们认识演员并干扰拍摄。
And also in the threesome you can find a scene with Donneld Trump.
在三人组中，您还可以找到与唐纳德·特朗普的场景。
And this is where the popularity of the franchise begins in earnest.
这就是该系列真正受欢迎的开始。
Film 1-house-3 create a reposition were replaced and past the calisters,
电影 1-house-3 创建了重新定位，并更换了卡器，
on the character's feet, since Glanu Hero, by that time already
在角色的脚上，从格拉努英雄开始，到那时已经
grew up and was not suitable for this film.
长大了，不适合这部电影。
In addition, the locations of two petty thieves appeared in the film
此外，片中还出现了两个小偷的地点
four beer.
四杯啤酒。
The fans didn't like it, because that's not what they stand for
粉丝不喜欢它，因为这不是他们所代表的
loved the movie.
喜欢这部电影。
Because of this, it is assembled much smaller than the other parts.
因此，它的组装尺寸比其他部件小得多。
You will come running 3-2 million dollars, the collection amounted to
你将带着3-200万美元前来，收集金额为
in 7-dvit000 dollars.
7-dvit000 美元。
I have to despite this.
尽管如此，我还是必须这么做。
I really love this part.
我真的很喜欢这一部分。
This was the first part that looked with the Donneld Franchise.
这是与唐纳德系列合作的第一部分。
However, if I want to review something first
但是，如果我想先回顾一下某些内容
three parts of Dindom, that is, if he is not part,
Dindom 的三个部分，也就是说，如果他不是一部分，
it goes by the wayside.
它就在路边。
In the rain, the Franchises have lost the third part, and the fourth.
在雨中，球队输掉了第三部分和第四部分。
Odindolln-4 was a killer.
Odindolln-4 是一名杀手。
Its budget was 5 million dollars.
其预算为500万美元。
Go straight from Maker.
直接从 Maker 出发。
The picture was absolutely amazing.
这张照片绝对是惊人的。
And we even decided to remove such panel things as traps.
我们甚至决定移除诸如陷阱之类的面板东西。
No, they were.
不，他们是。
But in very small quantities.
但数量非常少。
And for protection, mainly at the price of a smart home.
而为了保护，主要是以智能家居的价格。
There is no point in talking further about the remaining two parts.
剩下的两部分就没有必要再讨论了。
Kuzi.
库兹。
Or Kalka knows him in the west of Hyuga.
或者卡尔卡在日向西边认识他。
He was popular among them thanks to the parogram.
由于这个 parogram，他在他们中间很受欢迎。
Call your cousin.
打电话给你表弟。
In this program you had to call at a specific
在此程序中，您必须调用特定的
number.
数字。
If you managed to get through, you could go through the group
如果你成功通过了，你就可以通过该组
in front of the network country.
网络国家面前。
You might even get a refund for it.
您甚至可能会获得退款。
I will warn you because of Kuzya if the video is about the New Year.
如果视频是关于新年的，我会因为 Kuzya 的原因警告你。
I'll explain now.
我现在就解释一下。
Starting two thousand years ago, the show lost popularity.
从两千多年前开始，这个节目就失去了人气。
And this leads to the fact that even more nationalities appeared
这导致了更多民族的出现
game series.
游戏系列。
There are two games in the middle of them.
中间有两场比赛。
Kuzi New Year and Kuzi New Year two.
苦子年有苦子年两种。
The first participation is more kind.
第一次参与比较亲切。
The sad thing is that it's a small town
遗憾的是这是一个小镇
with Santa Claus preparing for the New Year.
与圣诞老人一起准备新年。
But a friend came, a witch, and ruined everything.
但一个朋友的到来，一个女巫，毁了一切。
And Kuzi is now helping to restore all this.
而库兹现在正在帮助恢复这一切。
We have an atmospheric map to go to
我们有一张大气地图可以去
home assignments.
家庭作业。
The tasks themselves are located randomly.
任务本身是随机定位的。
Because of this, finding them will be very difficult.
正因为如此，找到他们将会非常困难。
There are also grandfather frosts on the square, who
广场上还有霜爷爷，
wow told.
哇告诉。
The game ends with the witch checking that
游戏以女巫检查结束
happening in the city.
发生在城市里。
She looks from the ball and sees that there is no one there in the snow
她从球上看去，发现雪地里空无一人
doesn't work.
不起作用。
But if we move into reality, then in fact
但如果我们进入现实，那么事实上
This is just a picture that Kuzi made.
这只是库兹制作的一张照片。
But there was one banned at the moment.
但目前有一项被禁止。
This ending could be seen without completing the game.
这个结局不用完成游戏就可以看到。
To do this, you could simply exit the game and that’s it.
为此，您只需退出游戏即可。
Fans, when we finished this game, we really wanted
粉丝们，当我们完成这款游戏时，我们真的很想要
second part.
第二部分。
But once it worked out, they were disappointed.
但结果出来后，他们却很失望。
The city was completely removed from the game.
该城市已完全从游戏中移除。
Serzhat has changed a lot.
谢尔扎特改变了很多。
Also, the minigames are very simple.
此外，小游戏非常简单。
And the game itself is kind of cheap.
而且游戏本身也很便宜。
But why did this happen?
但为什么会发生这种情况呢？
The thing is that the first part was made by IT Copper.
问题是，第一部分是由 IT Copper 制作的。
Published by Media Chaos.
由混沌媒体出版。
Media Chaos saw that this part became very popular.
Media Chaos 看到这部分变得非常受欢迎。
And I decided to buy the rights from IT Media to make the second part.
我决定从 IT Media 购买制作第二部分的版权。
As a result, they finished the second part.
结果，他们完成了第二部分。
But naturally their budget was much smaller.
但自然他们的预算要少得多。
Why did the game turn out to be wasteful?
为什么游戏最终会变成浪费呢？
And no one liked her.
而且没有人喜欢她。
That's all I have.
这就是我所拥有的一切。
Thank you very much for watching these videos.
非常感谢您观看这些视频。
Like and subscribe to our community.
喜欢并订阅我们的社区。
Everyone was Pirkot.
每个人都是皮尔科特。
Video coming soon.
视频即将推出。
Goodbye.
再见。